A Guide to the Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- HB 2141 (01) Authority of Landlord to Sell Personal Property Removed from Premises (Box 43, Folder 10)
- HB 2142 (01) Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation, Civil Penalties (Box 43, Folder 11)
- HB 2144 (01) School Accreditation and College Admission (Box 43, Folder 12)
- HB 2145 (01) Low-income Housing Tax Credit (Box 43, Folder 13)
- HB 2149 (01) State Parks; Unlawful Use and Prohibited Parking (Box 43, Folder 14)
- HB 2152 (01) Regulations to Prevent Spread of Rabies in Fairfax County (Box 43, Folder 15)
- HB 2153 (01) Practitioners; Data Required for Felony Conviction (Box 43, Folder 16)
- HB 2157 (01) Insurance Transactions; Privacy, Consumer Protection (Box 43, Folder 17)
- HB 2158 (01) Securities Act; Broker-Dealers (Box 43)
- HB 2159 (01) Beryl R. Newman Memorial Highway (Box 43, Folder 19)
- HB 2160 (01) Beryl R. Newman Memorial Bridge (Box 43, Folder 20)
- HB 2161 (01) Money Order Sales and Money Transmission Services (Box 43, Folder 21)
- HB 2162 (01) Foreign Corporations; Domestication and Conversion (Box 43, Folder 22)
- HB 2165 (01) Certain Historic Properties; Notification Prior to Sale (Box 43, Folder 23)
- HB 2168 (01) Center for Innovative Technology (Box 43, Folder 24)
- HB 2169 (01) Agencies' and Court Clerks' Disclosure of Certain Account Information (Box 43, Folder 25)
- HB 2170 (01) Parking Regulation in Chesterfield County (Box 43, Folder 26)
- HB 2171 (01) Fingerprinting of Fire Department Applicants in Arlington County (Box 43, Folder 27)
- HB 2173 (01) Scooters, Limits Use on Highways in Arlington County (Box 43, Folder 28)
- HB 2174 (01) Certification of Residential Home Inspectors (Box 43, Folder 29)
- HB 2175 (01) ABC; Special Licenses for Motor Sports Road Racing (Box 43, Folder 30)
- HB 2176 (01) Continuation of State Aid to Certain Localities (Box 43, Folder 31)
- HB 2177 (01) Staunton Scenic River (Box 43, Folder 32)
- HB 2178 (01) Community Criminal Justice Boards (Box 43, Folder 33)
- HB 2180 (01) Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission and Fund (Box 43, Folder 34)
- HB 2181 (01) Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Fund (Box 43, Folder 35)
- HB 2182 (01) Property Tax Exemptions; Omnibus Bill (Box 43, Folder 36)
- HB 2183 (01) Procurement of Architectural or Professional Engineering Services (Box 43, Folder 37)
- HB 2185 (01) Health Insurance Accounts; State Employees; DHRM to Report (Box 43, Folder 38)
- HB 2189 (01) Criminal Cases; Tolling or Suspension of Statutes of Limitation (Box 43, Folder 39)
- HB 2190 (01) People with Disabilities Board (Box 43, Folder 40)
- HB 2198 (01) Warning Devices on Certain Ice Cream, Snack, etc. Trucks (Box 43, Folder 41)
- HB 2199 (01) Temporary Recall of Retired Judges (Box 43, Folder 42)
- HB 2200 (01) Suits Upon Judgment and Contracts of Decedent (Box 43, Folder 43)
- HB 2202 (01) Neighborhood Assistance Programs; Tax Credits (Box 43, Folder 44)
- HB 2204 (01) Misdemeanants; Release on Board (Box 43, Folder 45)
- HB 2205 (01) Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission; Jurisdiction over Judges (Box 43, Folder 46)
- HB 2211 (01) Voter Registration; Cancellation of Registration (Box 43, Folder 47)
- HB 2215 (01) Modification of Spousal Support Awards (Box 43, Folder 48)
- HB 2216 (01) Residential Landlord Tenant Act (Box 43, Folder 49)
- HB 2217 (01) Use of Highways by Motorcycles (Box 43, Folder 50)
- HB 2219 (01) Trucks Hauling Gravel, Sand or Crushed Stone (Box 43, Folder 51)
- HB 2220 (01) Liens on Real Estate and Personal Property for Unpaid Severance Taxes (Box 43, Folder 52)
- HB 2223 (01) Agricultural or Forestry Product, Facility or Animal (Box 43, Folder 53)
- HB 2224 (01) Commonwealth Mass Transit Funds (Box 43, Folder 54)
- HB 2228 (01) Long-Term Care Insurance; Rating Practices Disclosure; Study (Box 43, Folder 55)
- HB 2233 (01) Record of Undervoted and Overvoted Ballots (Box 43, Folder 56)
- HB 2235 (01) Limited Liability Companies; Conversion, Membership and Distributions (Box 43, Folder 57)
- HB 2236 (01) Small Business Advisory Board; Membership (Box 43, Folder 58)
- HB 2239 (01) Motor Vehicles; Penalty for Failure to Stop at Accident (Box 43, Folder 59)
- HB 2241 (01) Appointment to Regional Industrial Facilities Authority Board (Box 43, Folder 60)
- HB 2245 (01) Practice of Nursing (Box 43, Folder 61)
- HB 2250 (01) Wines; Sales by Farm Wineries (Box 43, Folder 62)
- HB 2255 (01) Mutual Insurers; Conversion to Stock Insurers, etc. (Box 43, Folder 63)
- HB 2268 (01) Notice of Proposed Location of Utility Lines (Box 43, Folder 64)
- HB 2269 (01) Confinement and Disposition of Animals by Animal Shelters (Box 43, Folder 65)
- HB 2271 (01) Powers and Duties of Clerks of the General District Courts (Box 43, Folder 66)
- HB 2272 (01) Health; Verbal Orders in Hospitals (Box 43, Folder 67)
- HB 2273 (01) Virginia Tech/Montgomery Regional Airport Authority (Box 43, Folder 68)
- HB 2274 (01) Bone Marrow Donation; Information on Driver's License (Box 43, Folder 69)
- HB 2278 (01) Care of Confederate Cemeteries and Graves (Box 43, Folder 70)
- HB 2281 (01) Registration Required of Persons Convicted of Sexual Offenses (Box 43, Folder 71)
- HB 2287 (01) Consumer Utility Tax; Exempt for Churches, Parks and Playgrounds (Box 43, Folder 72)
- HB 2289 (01) Claims, Harold C. Taylor (Box 43, Folder 73)
- HB 2290 (01) Child Support Guidelines (Box 43, Folder 74)
- HB 2292 (01) Nontidal Wetlands; Effective Date (Box 43, Folder 75)
- HB 2293 (01) VRS; Purchase of Prior Service Credit; Sick Leave (Box 43, Folder 76)
- HB 2294 (01) Hunting, Trapping and Fishing Licenses; Point of Sale (Box 43, Folder 77)
- HB 2302 (01) Littering in State Parks (Box 43, Folder 78)
- HB 2303 (01) VDOT Contracts (Box 43, Folder 79)
- HB 2304 (01) Assisting Other Hunters After Reaching Limit (Box 43, Folder 80)
- HB 2305 (01) Veterans Care Center (Box 43, Folder 81)
- HB 2306 (01) Workers' Compensation; Drug-Free Workplace Programs (Box 43, Folder 82)
- HB 2307 (01) Manufacturers to Evaluation Dealership Performance (Box 43, Folder 83)
- HB 2310 (01) Lake Level Contingency Plans (Box 43, Folder 84)
- HB 2312 (01) Mandatory Connection to Water and Sewage Systems (Box 43, Folder 85)
- HB 2313 (01) ABC; Wine for Judging (Box 43, Folder 86)
- HB 2315 (01) Attorney General; Settlement of Disputes, Claims and Controversies (Box 43, Folder 87)
- HB 2318 (01) Prescriptive Authority of Physician Assistants; Effectiveness Study (Box 43, Folder 88)
- HB 2322 (01) Farm-Use Vehicles (Box 43, Folder 89)
- HB 2323 (01) Campaign Finance Disclosure Act; Reporting Requirements (Box 43, Folder 90)
- HB 2325 (01) Campaign Finance Disclosure Act; Expenditures Made With Credit Card (Box 43, Folder 91)
- HB 2327 (01) Concealed Weapons by Convicted Felons (Box 43, Folder 92)
- HB 2329 (01) Capital Access Fund for Disadvantaged Businesses (Box 43, Folder 93)
- HB 2330 (01) Jurisdiction in Conservation Matters (Box 44, Folder 1)
- HB 2332 (01) Motor Vehicle Dealers; Damages Caused by Statutory Violations (Box 44, Folder 2)
- HB 2337 (01) Claims; John Thomas McCambridge (Box 44, Folder 3)
- HB 2340 (01) Juvenile Justice Information System (Box 44, Folder 4)
- HB 2342 (01) Exchange of Fuel Tax Information (Box 44, Folder 5)
- HB 2344 (01) Statewide Building Code; Inspection Warrants (Box 44, Folder 6)
- HB 2346 (01) Emergency Medical Services; Administration of Epinephrine (Box 44, Folder 7)
- HB 2352 (01) Victim Participation in Plea Agreements (Box 44, Folder 8)
- HB 2355 (01) Levy of Excise Tax on Apples (Box 44, Folder 9)
- HB 2356 (01) Modification of Sentencing Guidelines for Methamphetamine (Box 44, Folder 10)
- HB 2357 (01) Leave for Service with Volunteer Fire Department or Rescue Squad (Box 44, Folder 11)
- HB 2358 (01) Regulation and Inspection of Septic Tanks in Augusta County (Box 44, Folder 12)
- HB 2360 (01) Arts and Cultural District in Charlottesville and Harrisonburg (Box 44, Folder 13)
- HB 2363 (01) Liens for Gas Utilities Charges (Box 44, Folder 14)
- HB 2366 (01) Summonses Issued by Attorneys (Box 44, Folder 15)
- HB 2372 (01) Number of Witnesses Whose Depositions May be Taken (Box 44, Folder 16)
- HB 2373 (01) Secretary of the Commonwealth; Will Information Registration (Box 44, Folder 17)
- HB 2374 (01) Lawsuits Against Deceased Defendants; Appointment of Executor (Box 44, Folder 18)
- HB 2375 (01) Charitable Gaming Commission; Regulations, Study Bingo Halls (Box 44, Folder 19)
- HB 2376 (01) Relief from Legal Determination of Paternity (Box 44, Folder 20)
- HB 2378 (01) Family Day Homes; Criminal Record Waiver (Box 44, Folder 21)
- HB 2379 (01) Criminal History Record Information; Motor Carrier License (Box 44, Folder 22)
- HB 2380 (01) Motor Carriers (Box 44, Folder 23)
- HB 2387 (01) Computer Information Transactions Act; Consumer Protection (Box 44, Folder 24)
- HB 2388 (01) Nursing Homes; Barrier Crimes (Box 44, Folder 25)
- HB 2395 (01) Commercial, Promotional and Corporate Partnerships, etc. in Schools (Box 44, Folder 26)
- HB 2397 (01) Enforcement, etc., of Costs Imposed by State Bar Disciplinary Board (Box 44, Folder 27)
- HB 2401 (01) Standards of Quality; Literacy Passports, Diplomas, etc. (Box 44, Folder 28)
- HB 2405 (01) Certain Benefits for Special Forest Wardens (Box 44, Folder 29)
- HB 2406 (01) Andrew Lewis Memorial Highway (Box 44, Folder 30)
- HB 2411 (01) Electronic Transactions Act; Technical Amendments (Box 44, Folder 31)
- HB 2412 (01) Computer Information Transactions Act (Box 44, Folder 32)
- HB 2414 (01) Sales Tax Exemptions; Spacecraft Activities (Box 44, Folder 33)
- HB 2417 (01) Hydraulic Dredges; Clams (Box 44, Folder 34)
- HB 2418 (01) Submission of Claims to Department of Transportation (Box 44, Folder 35)
- HB 2419 (01) Management of the Commonwealth's Central Vehicle Fleet (Box 44, Folder 36)
- HB 2420 (01) Statewide Transportation Plan (Box 44, Folder 37)
- HB 2421 (01) Issuance of Governor's Warrant of Arrest (Box 44, Folder 38)
- HB 2422 (01) Assistant Commissioner for Environment, Transportation Planning, etc. (Box 44, Folder 39)
- HB 2424 (01) Civil Actions; Insurer's Reservation of Rights (Box 44, Folder 40)
- HB 2427 (01) Telephone Privacy Protection Act (Box 44, Folder 41)
- HB 2428 (01) Condominium and Property Owners' Association Acts (Box 44, Folder 42)
- HB 2429 (01) Common Interest Community Management Information Fund (Box 44, Folder 43)
- HB 2430 (01) Board of Nursing Home Administrators (Box 44, Folder 44)
- HB 2433 (01) Notification to Localities of State Construction (Box 44, Folder 45)
- HB 2438 (01) Powers of Redevelopment and Housing Authorities (Box 44, Folder 46)
- HB 2439 (01) Charter Schools (Box 44, Folder 47)
- HB 2442 (01) Affordable Housing in Arlington County (Box 44, Folder 48)
- HB 2443 (01) Local Taxes; Deduction of Taxes from Warrants by Treasurer (Box 44, Folder 49)
- HB 2444 (01) Parking Fines; Personal Property Taxes on Vehicles (Box 44, Folder 50)
- HB 2453 (01) Charter; Town of Wise (Box 44, Folder 51)
- HB 2454 (01) Payment of Fees by Credit Card (Box 44, Folder 52)
- HB 2463 (01) Human Cloning (Box 44, Folder 53)
- HB 2464 (01) Department of Employment Dispute Resolution; Review of Grievance Hearing Decisions (Box 44, Folder 54)
- HB 2468 (01) Industrial Development Authorities in Norfolk City (Box 44, Folder 55)
- HB 2471 (01) Mortgage Lender and Broker Act; Exemption for Real Estate Brokers (Box 44, Folder 56)
- HB 2472 (01) Electric Utility Restructuring; Renewable Energy (Box 44, Folder 57)
- HB 2473 (01) Home Energy Assistance Program; DSS to Report on Effectiveness (Box 44, Folder 58)
- HB 2476 (01) Disclosure of Proffered Cash Payments and Expenditures (Box 44, Folder 59)
- HB 2478 (01) Defeating Drug and Alcohol Screening Tests; Penalty (Box 44, Folder 60)
- HB 2479 (01) Capital Region Airport Commission (Box 44, Folder 61)
- HB 2481 (01) Labor and Employment; Remedies for Discrimination (Box 44, Folder 62)
- HB 2482 (01) Motor Vehicle Dealers (Box 44, Folder 63)
- HB 2483 (01) Bodily Injuries Caused by Accused Persons, Prisoners, etc. (Box 44, Folder 64)
- HB 2485 (01) VASAP Case Manager's Oath of Office (Box 44, Folder 65)
- HB 2486 (01) Reinstatement of Driver's License for Driving While Intoxicated (Box 44, Folder 66)
- HB 2487 (01) Court of Appeals (Box 44, Folder 67)
- HB 2488 (01) Civil Immunity and Privileged Communications; Medical Malpractice (Box 44, Folder 68)
- HB 2490 (01) Assisted Living Facilities; Dementia Residents (Box 44, Folder 69)
- HB 2491 (01) Involuntary Commitment Hearing (Box 44, Folder 70)
- HB 2493 (01) Oysters; Grants for Transfer to Sanctuary (Box 44, Folder 71)
- HB 2495 (01) Hampton Roads Museum Consortium (Box 44, Folder 72)
- HB 2496 (01) Review of Board of Zoning Appeals Decisions (Box 44, Folder 73)
- HB 2497 (01) Certificates of Veterinary Inspection for Fish or Invertebrate (Box 44, Folder 74)
- HB 2502 (01) Cultural Diversity Competency Training for Law Enforcement Officers (Box 44, Folder 75)
- HB 2512 (01) Student Discipline (Box 44, Folder 76)
- HB 2514 (01) Teacher Proficiency; Continuing Contract Status (Box 44, Folder 77)
- HB 2515 (01) Condominium and Property Owners' Association Acts; Disclosure Packets (Box 44, Folder 78)
- HB 2516 (01) Athletic Trainers; Certification (Box 44, Folder 79)
- HB 2517 (01) Compensation of Members of Commissions, etc., in Executive Branch (Box 44, Folder 80)
- HB 2519 (01) Private Security Services Businesses (Box 44, Folder 81)
- HB 2524 (01) Dr. Ralph Stanley Highway (Box 44, Folder 82)
- HB 2527 (01) Unemployment Rates in State; Economic Development Authority to Report on Plan (Box 44, Folder 83)
- HB 2528 (01) Coal and Gas and Improvement Tax (Box 44, Folder 84)
- HB 2531 (01) Charter; City of Norton (Box 44, Folder 85)
- HB 2532 (01) Public-Private Partnership for Provision of Water and Waste Services (Box 44, Folder 86)
- HB 2533 (01) Social Services; Adult Protective Services (Box 44, Folder 87)
- HB 2537 (01) State Employee Health Insurance Plan (Box 44, Folder 88)
- HB 2543 (01) Charter; Town of Front Royal (Box 44, Folder 89)
- HB 2546 (01) Exemptions from Licenses to Hunt, Trap, etc. by Tribe Members (Box 44, Folder 90)
- HB 2549 (01) Emblems of the Commonwealth; Official Gold Mining Interpretive Center (Box 44, Folder 91)
- HB 2554 (01) Provisional Driver's Licenses (Box 44, Folder 92)
- HB 2559 (01) Henderson Road in Fairfax County (Box 44, Folder 93)
- HB 2563 (01) Woodrow Wilson Memorial Bridge (Box 44, Folder 94)
- HB 2564 (01) Appointment to Industrial Development Authorities (Box 44, Folder 95)
- HB 2565 (01) Advantage Virginia Incentive Program (Box 44, Folder 96)
- HB 2570 (01) Informed Written Consent for Abortion (Box 44, Folder 97)
- HB 2575 (01) Search warrants (Box 45, Folder 1)
- HB 2576 (01) Mortgage lenders; notice of change of address to insurers (Box 45, Folder 2)
- HB 2577 (01) Expenses incurred in responding to DUI incident (Box 45, Folder 3)
- HB 2578 (01) When interest to be paid on award of restitution (Box 45, Folder 4)
- HB 2580 (01) Counsel in capital cases (Box 45, Folder 5)
- HB 2583 (01) Income tax; contribution of refunds to education (Box 45, Folder 6)
- HB 2585 (01) Comprehensive services act for at-risk youth and families (Box 45, Folder 7)
- HB 2588 (01) Reciprocity for criminal history records check by school boards (Box 45, Folder 8)
- HB 2589 (01) Teaching scholarship loan program (Box 45, Folder 9)
- HB 2593 (01) Identity fraud (Box 45, Folder 10)
- HB 2595 (01) DMHMRSAS: licensing (Box 45, Folder 11)
- HB 2599 (01) Senator M. M. Long highway (Box 45, Folder 12)
- HB 2601 (01) Discharges into state waters; notification required (Box 45, Folder 13)
- HB 2603 (01) Outdoors foundation; retirement plan (Box 45, Folder 14)
- HB 2606 (01) Northern Virginia transportation authority; study continued (Box 45, Folder 15)
- HB 2607 (01) No-discharge zone on Smith Mountain lake (Box 45, Folder 16)
- HB 2610 (01) Release of mental health information for concealed handgun permit (Box 45, Folder 17)
- HB 2612 (01) Care of confederate cemeteries and graves (Box 45, Folder 18)
- HB 2613 (01) Waiver of inventory and settlement for certain estates (Box 45, Folder 19)
- HB 2615 (01) Trapping license for disabled persons (Box 45, Folder 20)
- HB 2623 (01) Fingerprinting for concealed weapons permit (Box 45, Folder 21)
- HB 2617 (01) Board of trustees of the Virginia Museum of natural history (Box 45, Folder 22)
- HB 2629 (01) VRS; partial lump-sum payment option (Box 45, Folder 23)
- HB 2631 (01) Carnal knowledge of certain jail inmates, etc. (Box 45, Folder 24)
- HB 2637 (01) Complimentary hunting and fishing licenses (Box 45, Folder 25)
- HB 2640 (01) Telephone cooperatives (Box 45, Folder 26)
- HB 2641 (01) Judicial conference of Virginia for district courts (Box 45, Folder 27)
- HB 2646 (01) Unqualified person who votes (Box 45, Folder 28)
- HB 2649 (01) Overweight permits; trucks hauling concrete (Box 45, Folder 29)
- HB 2651 (01) Income tax; checkoff for contributions to promote organ and tissue donation (Box 45, Folder 30)
- HB 2654 (01) Health insurance; prescription benefit cards (Box 45, Folder 31)
- HB 2655 (01) Bank investments (Box 45, Folder 32)
- HB 2656 (01) Gordon C. Willis, Sr., smart road (Box 45, Folder 33)
- HB 2657 (01) Insurance; unfair claim settlement practices in accident appraisals (Box 45, Folder 34)
- HB 2663 (01) Classification of real property; land and improvements (Box 45, Folder 35)
- HB 2667 (01) Siting of landfills in Mecklenburg county (Box 45, Folder 36)
- HB 2670 (01) Outdoor advertising; variable message signs (Box 45, Folder 37)
- HB 2671 (01) Special transportation/taxing district (Box 45, Folder 38)
- HB 2673 (01) DUI blood lab work (Box 45, Folder 39)
- HB 2674 (01) Standard diploma (Box 45, Folder 40)
- HB 2676 (01) Emergency protective orders; criminal information network (Box 45, Folder 41)
- HB 2678 (01) Uniform health referral form (Box 45, Folder 42)
- HB 2683 (01) Compensation of court-appointed counsel (Box 45, Folder 43)
- HB 2688 (01) Hampton veterans' highway (Box 45, Folder 44)
- HB 2691 (01) Garnishment of wages from unemployment benefits for child support (Box 45, Folder 45)
- HB 2693 (01) Workforce council; membership (Box 45, Folder 46)
- HB 2694 (01) Resource on pharmaceutical companies' free drug programs (Box 45, Folder 47)
- HB 2699 (01) Chesapeake regional olympic games compact (Box 45, Folder 48)
- HB 2701 (01) Release of mental health information for concealed handgun permit (Box 45, Folder 49)
- HB 2704 (01) Health services plans, licensed pharmacists (Box 45, Folder 50)
- HB 2705 (01) Marine resources commission; publication of proposed regulations (Box 45, Folder 51)
- HB 2706 (01) Truck covers on solid waste vehicles (Box 45, Folder 52)
- HB 2708 (01) Mortgage loans; prohibits "flipping" (Box 45, Folder 53)
- HB 2712 (01) Overtime compensation for firefighters and EMTs (Box 45, Folder 54)
- HB 2717 (01) Public-private transportation act of 1995: definitions (Box 45, Folder 55)
- HB 2718 (01) Virginia State Bar; eligibility to sit for bar examination (Box 45, Folder 56)
- HB 2720 (01) Annuities (Box 45, Folder 57)
- HB 2721 (01) Insurance; hedging transactions (Box 45, Folder 58)
- HB 2722 (01) Dismissal of action by nonsuit (Box 45, Folder 59)
- HB 2726 (01) Health; on-site sewage evaluations (Box 45, Folder 60)
- HB 2728 (01) Claims; Richard S. Copeland (Box 45, Folder 61)
- HB 2729 (01) Certification of organically produced food (Box 45, Folder 62)
- HB 2734 (01) Moccasin gap sanitation commission; abolished (Box 45, Folder 63)
- HB 2735 (01) Eligibility for industrial site development program (Box 45, Folder 64)
- HB 2737 (01) Fees for solid waste disposal (Box 45, Folder 65)
- HB 2738 (01) Early intervention services system (Box 45, Folder 66)
- HB 2743 (01) Research and technology advisory commission; created, study reports (Box 45, Folder 67)
- HB 2749 (01) Days of operation of clerks' offices (Box 45, Folder 68)
- HB 2750 (01) Freedom of information; closed meetings, scholastic records (Box 45, Folder 69)
- HB 2751 (01) First offender; drugs (Box 45, Folder 70)
- HB 2754 (01) School buses; speed limits (Box 45, Folder 71)
- HB 2757 (01) Board for accountancy; educational requirements for CPA certificate (Box 45, Folder 72)
- HB 2758 (01) Return of local real estate tax surplus funds in Albemarle county (Box 45, Folder 73)
- HB 2762 (01) Immunization against meningococcal disease at higher education institutions (Box 45, Folder 74)
- HB 2763 (01) Health; outpatient data collection (Box 45, Folder 75)
- HB 2774 (01) Resources authority; funding of public safety facilities (Box 45, Folder 76)
- HB 2777 (01) Standards of learning; resource guides (Box 45, Folder 77)
- HB 2778 (01) Line of duty act; inclusion of police chaplains (Box 45, Folder 78)
- HB 2786 (01) School board; definition (Box 45, Folder 79)
- HB 2787 (01) Mortgage lenders and brokers; predatory lending practices (Box 45, Folder 80)
- HB 2788 (01) Appointment of standing grievance panel in Henrico county (Box 45, Folder 81)
- HB 2789 (01) Escrow accounts; disbursement of funds (Box 45, Folder 82)
- HB 2790 (01) Natural gas consumption tax and local license tax on public utilities (Box 45, Folder 83)
- HB 2791 (01) Sunday sale of wine and beer (Box 45, Folder 84)
- HB 2795 (01) Commitment of serious juvenile offenders (Box 45, Folder 85)
- HB 2801 (01) Insurance; optional uninsured motorist coverage (Box 45, Folder 86)
- HB 2802 (01) Criminal procedure; retention of evidence (Box 45, Folder 87)
- HB 2814 (01) State recordation tax; amount to be taxed (Box 45, Folder 88)
- HB 2820 (01) Individual income tax (Box 45, Folder 89)
- HB 2824 (01) Identity fraud; assistance of the attorney general (Box 45, Folder 90)
- HB 2827 (01) Sewage sludge (Box 45, Folder 91)
- HB 2830 (01) Sales and use tax; commercial and industrial exemption, sunset extension (Box 45, Folder 92)
- HB 2835 (01) Property conveyance; Mulberry Hill in Charlotte County (Box 45, Folder 93)
- HB 2836 (01) Criminal background checks; adult substance abuse treatment programs (Box 45, Folder 94)
- HB 2841 (01) Disclosure that a juvenile is a suspect or has been arrested (Box 45, Folder 95)
- HB 2842 (01) Transmittal of information to Virginia Criminal information network (VCIN) (Box 45, Folder 96)
- HB 2848 (01) Shell building initiative (Box 45, Folder 97)
- HB 2849 (01) Recount procedures (Box 45, Folder 98)
- HB 2850 (01) Annexation (Box 45, Folder 99)
- HB 2855 (01) Tourism authority; travel guide for disabled persons (Box 45, Folder 100)
- HB 2858 (01) Property conveyance; Mary B. Stratton estate (Box 45, Folder 101)
- HB 2859 (01) Virginia-Asian advisory board (Box 45, Folder 102)
- HB 2860 (01) Establishes a law enforcement accreditation center (Box 45, Folder 103)
- HB 2864 (01) Copies of health care provider's records and papers (Box 45, Folder 104)
- HB 2865 (01) Annual report on state spending by JLARC (Box 45, Folder 105)
- HB 2871 (01) Exceptions to certain private security licensing requirements (Box 45, Folder 106)